Guide to the Reston Black Focus records, 1960-2005
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 8: General Information, 1960-2005; (1.5 boxes)
  - Advertisements, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Austin L. Spriggs Architect-Planner, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Biographical Sketch-Edward G. Sharp, 2000s (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Biography, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Blank Stationary and Envelops, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors List, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Books About the Negro American, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Fact Sheet, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Festival Flyer, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Flyer, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Flyer, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Focus in Black-A Reston Festival (2 copies), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Fry and Welch Associates, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Handwritten List, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Handwritten Notes, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Handwritten Notes, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Health Committee, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Howard University Mississippi Project Fact Sheet, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - HMVC Communication Committee, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - In Memorian-Margaret Givens Young, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - In Memoriam-Lafayette James Holland, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Instruction, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Kid Power, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - List of Addresses, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - List of Builders in Reston, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Lots at Reston, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Maps (2 copies), 1970s (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Memorial Service-James Edward Givens, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Memorial Service-Jessie Clifton Holland (4 copies), 2005 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous Cards, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous Note, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Monarch-Carnival Supply Company (5 copies), 1970s (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Notes, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Note, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Notes, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Notes, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Notes, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Note, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Notes, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Note, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Note, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Notes, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Note, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Note, 2000s (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Note-Editor Reston Times, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Of Black America, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - One Hundredth Birthday Celebration for Jessie C. Holland, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Recommendations, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Reston Black Focus [Non] Distribution List, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - "Reston-Special To Black Men" by Edward G. Sharp, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Reston Tennis Association Membership Form, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Royce Hanson-Resume, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Schedule of Events, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Schedule of Events, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Schmitt's Florist Website, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Sharp Family (2 copies), 1970s (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Social Services List, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Study Team on Reston Homeowners Association (RHOA) Structure and Role, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Sulton and Campbell, American Institute of Architects (AIA), 1960s (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Tentative Schedule of Events, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - "The Slave Trade", 1970s (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Westgate Research Park, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 28)